<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Outside In Business Consultants]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Outside In Business Consultants]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:38:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:38:54 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What We Do]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Pointing Business Owners Towards Success. Contact Us and we will respond to you shortly.</p>,<p>We are pleased to meet with our clients at their location or any one of our locations.</p>,<h2>What We&nbsp;Do</h2>,<p>Outside In Business Consultants is&nbsp;a management consulting group providing business leaders with simple yet&nbsp;powerful tools to&nbsp;help your business run&nbsp;more smoothly and&nbsp;more profitably.</p>,<p>If&nbsp;you know you&nbsp;need to&nbsp;focus on&nbsp;the "Big Picture" but&nbsp;can't seem to&nbsp;carve out&nbsp;the time, if&nbsp;you are&nbsp;looking to&nbsp;establish clear, actionable steps to&nbsp;meet your goals this year and&nbsp;into the&nbsp;future, you&nbsp;are not&nbsp;alone. Explore these pages and&nbsp;see if&nbsp;we've struck a&nbsp;chord with you. Our&nbsp;business is, simply put, to&nbsp;help you&nbsp;succeed!</p>,<p>Our&nbsp;strategic planning system was&nbsp;founded in&nbsp;1990 and&nbsp;has proven effective with hundreds of&nbsp;clients. Many clients return for&nbsp;updated plans periodically.</p>,<p>Over 80% of&nbsp;start-up&nbsp;businesses fail within their first five years. Our&nbsp;process of&nbsp;strategic planning, business planning, and&nbsp;development of&nbsp;the organizational structures has&nbsp;dramatically increased the&nbsp;success rate of&nbsp;businesses using these processes.</p>,<p>Thank you for your interest in Outside In Business Consultants. Please contact us if you have any questions or would like to set up a meeting to mutually see if our process is right for you.</p>,<p>Learn More. We Will Find a Right Way For Your Company's Growth and Help You Reach an Entirely New Market! Make your business grow today! Contact Us Today!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/what-we-do/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b17ce829-39f3-431b-b52c-03cad655025d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:38:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Company Vision]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are pleased to meet with our clients at your location or any one of our locations.</p>,<h1>Company Vision</h1>,<p><strong>Do&nbsp;you have a&nbsp;clear sense of&nbsp;what you&nbsp;want your business to&nbsp;look like in&nbsp;three years? Five years? How&nbsp;are you&nbsp;preparing in&nbsp;order to&nbsp;get there?</strong></p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/company-vision/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ad717da4-a73d-42e3-a168-0233be2af7e0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:30:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Strategic Planning</h1>,<p><strong>It is very easy for strategic planning to take a back seat to the daily "to-do" list—some call this the tyranny of the urgent. We'll help you make time for this crucial task. Your valuable time will be rewarded with these kinds of outcomes:</strong></p>,<ul><li>Discovering and documenting the long-term vision you as a business owner have for your business.</li><li>Competitive Analysis, examining your competitors and discovering your unique niche in the marketplace.</li><li>Examining core competencies and weaknesses within your organization, pinpointing ways to exploit competencies and minimize weaknesses.</li><li>Developing a three-year plan.</li><li>Getting it in writing: critical goals, action steps, lines of responsibility and timelines for making your critical goals happen.</li><li>Formulating a system to document processes and procedures for the company.</li></ul>,<p>Thinking through the big issues, then acting on them - it's a thing of beauty when it all comes together! We have a strong track record of helping business owners through the maze of questions and responsibilities and into a profitable, more manageable future.</p>,<p>Our strategic planning process is our most comprehensive consulting service. But choices are good. You can also opt for specific components of the process - you'll find these described in the rest of the "Services" section.</p>,<p>We Will Find a Right Way For Your Company's Growth and Help You Reach an Entirely New Market!Make your business grow today!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/it-is-very-easy-for-strategic-planning-to-take-a-back-seat-t/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0f410d64-95e8-4386-9d4b-6f5f3ce1b10c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:22:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>