<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Outside In Business Consultants]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Outside In Business Consultants]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:23:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:23:25 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>It&nbsp;is very easy for&nbsp;strategic planning to&nbsp;take a&nbsp;back seat to&nbsp;the daily "to-do" list—some call this the&nbsp;tyranny of&nbsp;the urgent. We'll help you&nbsp;make time for&nbsp;this crucial task. Your valuable time will be&nbsp;rewarded with these kinds of&nbsp;outcomes:</strong></p>,<ul><li>Discovering and&nbsp;documenting the&nbsp;long-term vision you&nbsp;as a&nbsp;business owner have for&nbsp;your business.</li><li>Competitive Analysis, examining your competitors and&nbsp;discovering your unique niche in&nbsp;the marketplace.</li><li>Examining core competencies and&nbsp;weaknesses within your organization, pinpointing ways to&nbsp;exploit competencies and&nbsp;minimize weaknesses.</li><li>Developing a&nbsp;three-year plan.</li><li>Getting it&nbsp;in writing: critical goals, action steps, lines of&nbsp;responsibility and&nbsp;timelines for&nbsp;making your critical goals happen.</li><li>Formulating a&nbsp;system to&nbsp;document processes and&nbsp;procedures for&nbsp;the company.&nbsp;</li></ul>,<p>Thinking through the&nbsp;big issues, then acting on&nbsp;them - it's a&nbsp;thing of&nbsp;beauty when it&nbsp;all comes together! We&nbsp;have a&nbsp;strong track record of&nbsp;helping business owners through the&nbsp;maze of&nbsp;questions and&nbsp;responsibilities and&nbsp;into a&nbsp;profitable, more manageable future.</p>,<p>Our&nbsp;strategic planning process is&nbsp;our most comprehensive consulting service. But&nbsp;choices are&nbsp;good. You&nbsp;can also opt&nbsp;for specific components of&nbsp;the process - you'll find these described in&nbsp;the rest of&nbsp;the "Services" section.&nbsp;</p>,<p>We Will Find a Right Way For Your Company's Growth and Help You Reach an Entirely New Market!Make your business grow today!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/it-is-very-easy-for-strategic-planning-to-take-a-back-seat-t/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0f410d64-95e8-4386-9d4b-6f5f3ce1b10c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:22:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are pleased to meet with our clients at their location or any one of our locations.</p>,<h2>Strategic Planning</h2>,<p>Outside In Business Consultants is a management consulting group providing business leaders with simple yet powerful tools to help your business run more smoothly and more profitably.</p>,<button data-role="cta">Contact Us</button>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/outside-in-business-consultants/strategic-planning/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">517c994c-35bf-4fd3-92a6-00ca052b68ff</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:06:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>